A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97)
1965-1997, 2004
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA471
410.4 Cubic Feet
Other Finding Aids note
For other open RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA479 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-1.15
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA477 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1994-1997.
Arrangement note
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Biographical/Historical note
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Rockefeller Foundation
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A94), 1966-1994; 1.20; 217.2 Cubic Feet; Record cartons R2728-R2895, R2880A, R2896-R2902, R2905, R2906-R2911, R9402 and R9403.
  Arrangement
  Arranged primarily by Program, with a small volume of records arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Scholars (Abramowitz), 1988-1992 (Box R2786)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - Scholars (Acha), 1987-1988 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Acheson), 1985-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Agung), 1989-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Akingbohungbe), 1987-1989 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Alagoa), 1988-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Alarcon), 1987-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Alschu1ar, A.), 1990-1992 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Altieri), 1988-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Aluko), 1986-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Alvarenga), 1990-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Alvim), 1986-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Anaya), 1990-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Arney), 1987-1988, 1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Arole), 1990-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Ashakul), 1988-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Assaad), 1987-1988, 1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Atlan), 1989-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Baglioni), 1988-1989 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Baier), 1990-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Bailey), 1988-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Bain), 1987-1989 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Barbedette), 1989-1991 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Bardach), 1988-1989 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Barker), 1988-1990 (Box R2786)
    - Scholars (Barker, E.), 1990-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Barnes), 1989-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Barnes, S.), 1989-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Barolini), 1989-1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Barry), 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bartra), 1990-1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Baslaw), 1988-1989 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bassett), 1987-1988 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bates), 1988-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Baumbach), 1988-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bearison), 1988-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Beckerman), 1988-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Beekman), 1988-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Belknap), 1987-1988, 1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bennani), 1990-1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Benstock), 1988-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bentley), 1990-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Benvenisti), 1989-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Berc), 1987-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bernays), 1989-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bernstein), 1986-1988 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Berry), 1987-1989, 1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bharucha), 1990-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bienkowski), 1987-1989 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Birnie), 1987-1988 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Biswas, S.), 1990-1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Black, J.M.), 1986-1990 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Blau), 1986-1989, 1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Blaustein), 1987-1989 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Bodea), 1989-1991 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Boe), 1986-1989 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Borresen), 1987-1988 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Botton-Beja), 1986-1988 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Boutis), 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2787)
    - Scholars (Brass), 1987-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Bok), 1990-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Brecher), 1987-1988 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Briseno), 1989-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Brombert), 1988-1992 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Broude), 1990-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Bruer, J.), 1989-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Bruer, L.), 1989-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Buckley), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Cahn), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Calisher), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Callaway), 1990-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Calvo), 1986-1988 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Cavalli-Sforza), 1990-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Cesar), 1987-1988 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chahal), 1990-1992 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chadwick), 1989-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chance), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Charlton), 1988-1989 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chase), 1989-1990 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chase, K.), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Cheshire), 1987-1989, 1992 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Chitr), 1987-1989 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Claman), 1990-1993 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Clampitt), 1990-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Coates), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Cohen), 1989-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Concepcion), 1987-1989 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Connor), 1988-1991 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Connors), 1988-1989 (Box R2788)
    - Scholars (Consoli), 1987-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Cook, A.), 1986-1987 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Coon), 1986-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Cotter), 1987-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Courtenay), 1988-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Coyne), 1989-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Cramton), 1986-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Cresswell), 1987-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Crowley), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dallin), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Danielpour), 1987-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Darby), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Datta-Munshi), 1987-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Davidson), 1990-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Davis), 1988-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Day, A. T.), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Day, L.H.), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (DeConde), 1987-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (DeCredico), 1988-1992 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (DeGeorge), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (DeLuca), 1987-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dening), 1990-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dennett), 1989-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Desowitz), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Deutch), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dickie), 1988-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Djerassi), 1989-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dolzer), 1985-1988 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Donagan, A.), 1990-1991 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Douglas), 1988-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dove), 1987-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dunlap), 1987-1989 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Drescher), 1989-1990 (Box R2789)
    - Scholars (Dunn, M.), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Dunn, R.), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Edel), 1988-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Edelman, M.), 1988-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Edelman, P.), 1988-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Edelstein), 1990-1992 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Ehrlich), 1988-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Eicher), 1986-1988 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Ejigou), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (El-Kheshen), 1987-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Elkin), 1987-1988, 1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Ely), 1989-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Engels), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Erb), 1987-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Erickson), 1986-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Escovitz), 1990-1992 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fabre), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Farley), 1988-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Faundes), 1987-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fawkes), 1985-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Feinberg), 1988-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Felder), 1985-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Figes), 1988-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Finger), 1988-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fleischer), 1989-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fletcher, R.), 1988-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fletcher, G.), 1985-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fogel), 1987-1989 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Fogelin), 1990-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Folarin), 1989-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Foot), 1989-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (France), 1988-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Francis, K. ), 1988-1990 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Francis, J.), 1988-1991 (Box R2790)
    - Scholars (Freed), 1988-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Freeland), 1987-1988 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Friedlander), 1986-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Friedrich O.), 1987-1990 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Freidson, E. ), 1989-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Friend, T. ), 1987-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Frykenberg, R. E.), 1987-1988 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gaddis. W.), 1987-1988 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gambari, I. A.), 1987-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Garcellano, E. E.), 1988-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Garrard, J.), 1987-1990 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gelber, J.), 1988-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Geller, T. ), 1988-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gergen, K. J.), 1990-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Ghadially, R.), 1988-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gibson, W. C.), 1986-1988, 1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gilbert, S. M.), 1990-1992 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gimblett), 1990-1992 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Goldscheider), 1987-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Goldstein), 1989-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Goodheart), 1988-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Goodman), 1988-1990 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gordon), 1987-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gornick), 1988-1989 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Grant), 1990-1992 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Green), 1990-1992 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Greenberg), 1989-1990 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Greenberg, J. ), 1988-1991 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Grodin), 1989-1990 (Box R2791)
    - Scholars (Gusfield), 1989-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hall), 1988-1992 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Halliday), 1988-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hamburger), 1987-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hampl), 1990-1992 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hansmann), 1988-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hardin), 1987-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Harleman), 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Harris), 1986 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Harteis), 1989-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Havis), 1986-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hayley, B.), 1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Healey), 1987-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hechinger), 1990-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Helfer), 1988-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hes), 1987-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hickman), 1988-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hiebert), 1988-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hill), 1988-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hill, E.), 1990-1992 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hoffmann), 1987-1988 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hollingsworth), 1989-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Home), 1989-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hooker), 1984-1985, 1987-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hoopes), 1989-1992 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Horowitz), 1989-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Howe), 1983-1984 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hoy), 1990-1991 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Huannou), 1988-1989 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hubert), 1988-1990 (Box R2792)
    - Scholars (Hubner), 1989-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Hudson), 1989-1992 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Huet), 1988-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Hughes, H.), 1989-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Hughes, R.), 1987-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Ikonne), 1988-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Husain), 1988-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Hyde), 1990-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Irele), 1987-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Iser), 1989-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Israeli), 1987-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Jacker), 1984-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (James), 1986-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Janouch), 1988-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Jennings), 1984, 1987-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Johnson, V.R.), 1986-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Johnson, D.), 1989-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Jolowicz), 1989-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Jones, B.), 1988-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Justice), 1990-1992 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kahn), 1991-1992 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kaplan, F.), 1988-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kaplan, J.), 1989-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kaufman), 1987-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kaufman, S.), 1987-1988 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Keeley), 1987-1989, 1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Keitel), 1986-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kekes), 1988-1990 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kerber), 1990-1991 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kerman), 1988-1989 (Box R2793)
    - Scholars (Kernis), 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kert), 1989-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Ketcham), 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kettler), 1987-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kety), 1988-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kinnell), 1986, 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kinsbourne), 1989-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kirshenblatt-Gimblett), 1990-1992 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kitzinger), 1987-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Klein), 1990-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Klein-Braley), 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Knauer), 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Knox), 1990-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kondoleon), 1989-1990, 1992 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Konstan), 1990-1992 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Korn), 1990-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Korshin), 1987-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Koscianski), 1988-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kowzan), 1988-1990, 1992 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Krieger), 1989-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kupperman) J.J., 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Kupperman) K.O., 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Laderman) E., 1982-1984, 1986 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Laderman) C., 1988-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Laclau), 1989-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Laderman) G., 1988-1989 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Lambeth), 1990-1991 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Lapidus) I., 1988-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Lapidus) G., 1989-1990 (Box R2794)
    - Scholars (Lashof), 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lassner), 1987-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Laszlo), 1987-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Laymon), 1988-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lee), 1986-1988 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Leeder), 1986-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Leigh), 1990-1992 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lerner) G., 1990-1992 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lerner) A., 1981, 1983-1984, 1989-1990 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lerner) R., 1988-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Letwin) S., 1990-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Letwin) W., 1990-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Levertov), 1988-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Levich), 1990-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Levine), 1990-1992 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lillyman), 1987-1990 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lindberg), 1990-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lipton), 1989-1990 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Livingston), 1988-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lockert), 1989-1990 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Loeb), 1989-1990, 1993 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Loescher), 1987-1988 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Lucas), 1987-1988 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Ludvigson), 1988-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Luria), 1988-1989 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (Luza), 1986-1988 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (McCabe), 1987-1988 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (McCloskey) D., 1990-1991 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (McCloskey) J., 1990-1992 (Box R2795)
    - Scholars (McElroy), 1988-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (MacAloon), 1987-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Mahony), 1988-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Makinwa-Adebusoye), 1987-1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Malajny), 1990-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Mann), 1990-1992 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Manor), 1988-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Marcus), 1989-1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Marqulis), 1988, 1990-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Martines), 1989-1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Marx), 1989-1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Matson), 1989-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Matthews), 1987-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Maxwell, J.P.), 1989-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (May, B.), 1986-1988, 1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (May, R.), 1989-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Maybury-Lewis), 1987-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Mayer), 1987-1988, 1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Megged), 1986-1988 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Meredith), 1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Merelman), 1989-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Merriam), 1988-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Merwick), 1990-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Michalek), 1987-1990 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Middlebrook), 1989-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Mignone), 1986-1988, 1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Milton), 1989-1992 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Monti), 1987-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Moore), 1988-1989 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Moosvi), 1990-1992 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Morgan, R.), 1988-1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Morrison), 1986-1988 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Morse), 1990-1992 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Munro), 1991 (Box R2796)
    - Scholars (Murphy), 1990-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Murray), 1989-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Narasimhaiah), 1985-1988, 1991-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Neipris), 1988-1990, 1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Nelson, B.), 1990-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ni), 1989-1990 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Nickisch), 1988-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Nowotny), 1986-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Nozick), 1987-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Obschatko), 1989-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ogunbadejo), 1990-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ohta), 1987-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ojaide), 1988-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Oke), 1990-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Oliver), 1990-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (O'Meara), 1987-1989, 1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ondaatje), 1988-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Orlans), 1988-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Orth), 1988-1989, 1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Ostendorf), 1989-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Oszlak), 1986-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Pammett), 1988-1989 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Paribatra), 1986-1988 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Park), 1988-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Paternosto), 1990-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Patterson), 1988-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Pedersen), 1982-1984 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Pellegrino), 1987-1988 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Perazzo), 1989-1990 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Peretz), 1988-1990 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Perin), 1991-1992 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Pettigrew), 1990-1991 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Phillips, Derek), 1987-1988 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Phillips, Dennis), 1988-1993 (Box R2797)
    - Scholars (Pitofsky), 1988-1991 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Platt), 1989-1990 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Platz), 1989-1990 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Pogany), 1988-1991 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Pomeroy), 1990-1991 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Pork), 1988-1990 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Raffauf), 1987-1988, 1990, 1992 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Raines), 1990-1992 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Rakowski), 1989-1991 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Ramazani), 1989-1991, 1994 (Box R2798)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2015. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - Scholars (Reid), 1990-1992 (Box R2798)
    - Scholars (Remini), 1988-1991 (Box R2798)